[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "What difference at this point does it make?", "question_tokens": ["What", "difference", "at", "this", "point", "does", "it", "make", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "And the NRA fires back at President Obama on guns.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "the", "NRA", "fires", "back", "at", "President", "Obama", "on", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "What was your verdict?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "verdict", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "What I thought is still so many questions that went unanswered and frankly some unsatisfactory answers.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "thought", "is", "still", "so", "many", "questions", "that", "went", "unanswered", "and", "frankly", "some", "unsatisfactory", "answers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "Well, where do we go with this?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "where", "do", "we", "go", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Piers, first of all, that's not what I'm saying.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "that", "'s", "not", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tunisia"]}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", ":", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "And I'm sure you would agree with that, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "'m", "sure", "you", "would", "agree", "with", "that", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "I fully agree that the whole goal of this is to make sure we get to the bottom of it so that it doesn't happen again and also so that we make sure -- I mean, one of the things, of course, we learned as well is we had someone in custody in Tunisia, that person has been released and we want to hold those accountable for -- who committed these horrible murders on our people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "fully", "agree", "that", "the", "whole", "goal", "of", "this", "is", "to", "make", "sure", "we", "get", "to", "the", "bottom", "of", "it", "so", "that", "it", "does", "n't", "happen", "again", "and", "also", "so", "that", "we", "make", "sure", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "one", "of", "the", "things", ",", "of", "course", ",", "we", "learned", "as", "well", "is", "we", "had", "someone", "in", "custody", "in", "Tunisia", ",", "that", "person", "has", "been", "released", "and", "we", "want", "to", "hold", "those", "accountable", "for", "--", "who", "committed", "these", "horrible", "murders", "on", "our", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Well, I think there are legitimate questions that still need to be answered.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "are", "legitimate", "questions", "that", "still", "need", "to", "be", "answered", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "I do agree with that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "agree", "with", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "When you take that line of political argument, should everybody just be fired every time any intelligence turns out to be not quite right?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "take", "that", "line", "of", "political", "argument", ",", "should", "everybody", "just", "be", "fired", "every", "time", "any", "intelligence", "turns", "out", "to", "be", "not", "quite", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "So we're going -- I don't think it's quite analogous to compare what happened during the Bush administration with what's happening right now.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "we", "'re", "going", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "quite", "analogous", "to", "compare", "what", "happened", "during", "the", "Bush", "administration", "with", "what", "'s", "happening", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Well, why not?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "-- a blanket standard of measures.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "a", "blanket", "standard", "of", "measures", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["earlier today"], "PERSON": ["Dick Durbin", "Dick Durbin", "Clinton"], "LOCATION": ["Dick"]}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "JJR", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "Because this is the Dick -- Dick Durbin argument from earlier today, this is what we heard from Dick Durbin earlier when he was questioning Secretary of State Clinton.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "this", "is", "the", "Dick", "--", "Dick", "Durbin", "argument", "from", "earlier", "today", ",", "this", "is", "what", "we", "heard", "from", "Dick", "Durbin", "earlier", "when", "he", "was", "questioning", "Secretary", "of", "State", "Clinton", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 138, "question": "What's the difference?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "But the bottom line is --", "answer_tokens": ["But", "the", "bottom", "line", "is", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "-- where are the mistakes made?", "question_tokens": ["--", "where", "are", "the", "mistakes", "made", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Dana.", "answer_tokens": ["Dana", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Are we going to talk about the Bush years or are we going to talk about what happened in Benghazi?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "going", "to", "talk", "about", "the", "Bush", "years", "or", "are", "we", "going", "to", "talk", "about", "what", "happened", "in", "Benghazi", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "I'm talking about what I --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "talking", "about", "what", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"], "LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Do you not think, Piers -- do you not think that it's legitimate to ask who manipulated these talking points?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "not", "think", ",", "Piers", "--", "do", "you", "not", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "legitimate", "to", "ask", "who", "manipulated", "these", "talking", "points", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Then why aren't we talking about that?", "question_tokens": ["Then", "why", "are", "n't", "we", "talking", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "There are many legitimate questions.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "many", "legitimate", "questions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Do you believe that at any stage either Susan Rice or Hillary Clinton has deliberately lied or deliberately misled the American people?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "at", "any", "stage", "either", "Susan", "Rice", "or", "Hillary", "Clinton", "has", "deliberately", "lied", "or", "deliberately", "misled", "the", "American", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "I think it's a serious charge and I think it's a false charge.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "serious", "charge", "and", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "false", "charge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Susan Rice", "Hillary Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "And now you have time to think about that, was there nothing that the president came out with in any of the 23 executive orders or any of the other proposals that you could at least consider?", "question_tokens": ["And", "now", "you", "have", "time", "to", "think", "about", "that", ",", "was", "there", "nothing", "that", "the", "president", "came", "out", "with", "in", "any", "of", "the", "23", "executive", "orders", "or", "any", "of", "the", "other", "proposals", "that", "you", "could", "at", "least", "consider", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBD", "EX", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, one of the interesting things about this, Piers, is that you asked me if I liked any of these.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "one", "of", "the", "interesting", "things", "about", "this", ",", "Piers", ",", "is", "that", "you", "asked", "me", "if", "I", "liked", "any", "of", "these", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Why would you -- why would you not like background checks?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "--", "why", "would", "you", "not", "like", "background", "checks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Including the NRA as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Including", "the", "NRA", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "So did you mislead me last time?", "question_tokens": ["So", "did", "you", "mislead", "me", "last", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Wait a minute.", "answer_tokens": ["Wait", "a", "minute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "What good are laws if people don't follow them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "good", "are", "laws", "if", "people", "do", "n't", "follow", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "So you still maintain that we just have to put more and more guns out there and America will be safer?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "still", "maintain", "that", "we", "just", "have", "to", "put", "more", "and", "more", "guns", "out", "there", "and", "America", "will", "be", "safer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "CC", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "I don't maintain anything.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "maintain", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Do you believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "And Piers, let me tell you something.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "Piers", ",", "let", "me", "tell", "you", "something", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "-- would lead to less gun crime?", "question_tokens": ["--", "would", "lead", "to", "less", "gun", "crime", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "MD", "VB", "TO", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Let me -- let me answer you.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "--", "let", "me", "answer", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Now, PJ, have you heard any convincing argument as to why that kind of weapon should remain in civilian hands?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "PJ", ",", "have", "you", "heard", "any", "convincing", "argument", "as", "to", "why", "that", "kind", "of", "weapon", "should", "remain", "in", "civilian", "hands", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "TO", "WRB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, I mean, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "What did you make of that, PJ?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "that", ",", "PJ", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Well, I mean, as you look at war, you know, there's no difference anymore in the current way that wars are fought between the front lines and the rear guard.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "as", "you", "look", "at", "war", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "difference", "anymore", "in", "the", "current", "way", "that", "wars", "are", "fought", "between", "the", "front", "lines", "and", "the", "rear", "guard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Why would they not be able to be as effective as many men in combat?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "they", "not", "be", "able", "to", "be", "as", "effective", "as", "many", "men", "in", "combat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Well, I would say the contradiction also exists with you, though.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "say", "the", "contradiction", "also", "exists", "with", "you", ",", "though", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "In all your time as a meteorologist, have you a sense now that we are going through a genuine climatic change in the weather?", "question_tokens": ["In", "all", "your", "time", "as", "a", "meteorologist", ",", "have", "you", "a", "sense", "now", "that", "we", "are", "going", "through", "a", "genuine", "climatic", "change", "in", "the", "weather", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Well, you can't attribute one particular event like this to climate change.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "attribute", "one", "particular", "event", "like", "this", "to", "climate", "change", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 429, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "I don't think there's any -- I think you're better off --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "'s", "any", "--", "I", "think", "you", "'re", "better", "off", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "I say you look at the peer reviewed literature.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "say", "you", "look", "at", "the", "peer", "reviewed", "literature", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "You wouldn't dispute there's been increased acceleration in CO2, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "n't", "dispute", "there", "'s", "been", "increased", "acceleration", "in", "CO2", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "No, CO2 is rising.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "CO2", "is", "rising", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Michael, over to you?", "question_tokens": ["Michael", ",", "over", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Yes, Piers, I haven't met Mark.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "have", "n't", "met", "Mark", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Midwest"]}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", ",", "RB", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Lee, what's the forecast for the next few days?", "question_tokens": ["Lee", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "forecast", "for", "the", "next", "few", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Just like I just thawed out, so will the Midwest and the northeast.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "like", "I", "just", "thawed", "out", ",", "so", "will", "the", "Midwest", "and", "the", "northeast", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "ORGAN: I hear you are wearing a battery packed heated jacket?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "I", "hear", "you", "are", "wearing", "a", "battery", "packed", "heated", "jacket", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "I got two battery packs in here.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "two", "battery", "packs", "in", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Did ABC find a few more dollars to finish off the gloves?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "ABC", "find", "a", "few", "more", "dollars", "to", "finish", "off", "the", "gloves", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "RBR", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I knitted them myself while we were away.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "knitted", "them", "myself", "while", "we", "were", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["ABC"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "What's your view about the debate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "view", "about", "the", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Guns are very serious instruments of survival and defense.", "answer_tokens": ["Guns", "are", "very", "serious", "instruments", "of", "survival", "and", "defense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Can you give me an answer?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "give", "me", "an", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "I don't know if I'll give you an answer that will satisfy your sense of -- you know, sane logic.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "I", "'ll", "give", "you", "an", "answer", "that", "will", "satisfy", "your", "sense", "of", "--", "you", "know", ",", "sane", "logic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "How do you possibly defend yourselves?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "possibly", "defend", "yourselves", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "Well, you know, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Knoxville"]}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "WRB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "But do you believe that any musician or movie star or movie maker or music producer, do they have any responsibility in terms of rhetoric about guns or the portrayal of them in movies?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "any", "musician", "or", "movie", "star", "or", "movie", "maker", "or", "music", "producer", ",", "do", "they", "have", "any", "responsibility", "in", "terms", "of", "rhetoric", "about", "guns", "or", "the", "portrayal", "of", "them", "in", "movies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "OAKAM: In case of point of (inaudible), that literally an extension of the tradition of -- there was an old blue grass song called \"Knoxville Girl,\" where for no reason -- it actually goes back to Irish guys who wrote folk songs.", "answer_tokens": ["OAKAM", ":", "In", "case", "of", "point", "of", "(", "inaudible", ")", ",", "that", "literally", "an", "extension", "of", "the", "tradition", "of", "--", "there", "was", "an", "old", "blue", "grass", "song", "called", "``", "Knoxville", "Girl", ",", "''", "where", "for", "no", "reason", "--", "it", "actually", "goes", "back", "to", "Irish", "guys", "who", "wrote", "folk", "songs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "These aren't unexploded grenades, right?", "question_tokens": ["These", "are", "n't", "unexploded", "grenades", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "No, they're not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "they", "'re", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Eddie, when you got that footage, what did you feel about it?", "question_tokens": ["Eddie", ",", "when", "you", "got", "that", "footage", ",", "what", "did", "you", "feel", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "I felt getting that footage was very revealing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "felt", "getting", "that", "footage", "was", "very", "revealing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "What were your emotions then?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "your", "emotions", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "Well, I mean, clearly, I was incredibly shocked and saddened.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "clearly", ",", "I", "was", "incredibly", "shocked", "and", "saddened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130123pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "More guns would lead to more safety at schools?", "question_tokens": ["More", "guns", "would", "lead", "to", "more", "safety", "at", "schools", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "TO", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "Well, I have to say, first off, that I'm a filmmaker.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "to", "say", ",", "first", "off", ",", "that", "I", "'m", "a", "filmmaker", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]